So now we are going to see how we can clone Mifare classic card.
So to clone Mifare classic card first we will crack the Mifare classic card and then we will clone it
to magic card.
So this is the same card which we used before in our previous video.
So let's just check out the Uid of this card.
So it's f.
14 a treat so that we get the Uuid.
Now we will note down this Uuid.
Over here so that we will use it later.
So I have no doubt this in the text editor and let's just check out all the keys.
So to check out all the keys, we use EMF and check command as we know.
And it's a classic one card.
And over here last time, what we did is we emulated all the keys into our emulator memory.
This time we are going to dump all the keys in a text file or a binary file.
You can say so to dump all the files into binary file, we have to use the command.
And let's just hit enter.
So all the files are dumped into bin file.
And over here, as you can see in sector five, Key A and B are unknown.
Other than that, all the keys are dumped into bin file.
And from now on, we know how to get the unknown keys through a nested attack.
So let's just run the nested attack.
Zfmf.
Nested.
And we are going to run it on one card with all the unknown factors.
And this time we are also going to dump the nested attack keys into a dump file.
So it will also create a bin file.
That's it.
Basically it will dump into the same bin file.
So let's just hit enter.
So you might get this error.
Sometimes all you have to do is you have to remove the card and replace it.
So now it's able to find all the keys.
As you can see it, Sector five keys are also found now and all the keys are now dumped into dump keys
dot bin file.
So by doing this, we have just dumped all the keys in the dumb keys file.
What we have to do is we have to also dump all the blocks data.
So to dump all the blocks data, what we have to do is we just have to run the dump command.
So it's.
And it's dump.
It's going to read all the blocks data and then it's going to write into a dump data dot bin file.
So, as you can see, dumped 64 blocks to file dump data dot bin.
So it's just created a dump data dot bin file.
Now we can load this file into a magic card, but before loading this file, what we have to do is we
have to convert this file to Elf format.
Now, we cannot load Ben file into magic card.
So to convert it into Elf format, first we have to exit.
And in the same client folder, there's another Python script which you have to run with Python keyword
and the script is pgm3 underscore MFD2ML.
So this is the script which you have to run and you have to provide the dump data dot bin file.
And then you have to provide the name of the file, which whatever name you want to give.
So I'm going to give.
Test file five and you have to give extension.
So let's just run it.
So test file five dot yaml file is created.
So what we have to do is we have to load this file into Proxmox three.
So let's just run proxmox three again.
So it's saying invalid serial port.
So all you have to do is you have to.
First disconnect.
And then exit.
And then you have to reconnect.
And then we'll run the same command.
So it's connected now.
So it happens sometime.
You just have to disconnect and reconnect.
Proxima three.
So let's just remove our previous card and let's just place the magic card on Proxmox three.
And first, let's just check out the Uuid of this card.
It's 14 a.
So as you can see, it's showing us the dummy.
Of this card.
So we will also check out all the blogs.
Give.
So to check out all the block keys, we have to run the check command.
And we can run check command with.
The option.
So as you can see, it's on the transport configuration because we can see all the keys.
Key A's and B's are showing in a transport mode.
So there's nothing changed in this card.
So what we are going to do is we are going to clone our previous card on this card.
So we already converted our file.
All we have to do is we have to run EMF and C load.
See load.
This is the command and we just have to provide the file name.
So the file name is test file.
Five and we just have to give the file name without extension.
So we will not type.
We will just provide the file name and let's just hit enter.
Okay, so the file is loaded into our magic card.
As we can see it over here.
So now let's just check out the.
The key is one more time.
So we will run f f.
Check command.
And we will run this command and execute all the keys in emulator.
So as you can see, Sector five is unknown as it was unknown in our actual card.
So we can do nested attack and check out the keys on this card as well.
We know the keys, but still we will do the attack and check out the keys.
For valid keys found and it has the same keys and it will contain the same data as the original Mifare
card.
So this is how you copy Mifare Classic card.
Now, let's just check out one more thing.
Let's just check out the UI of this card.
So the Uuid is also updated of this card.
Right.
But if the Uuid is sometime the Uuid is not updated in magic cards, so there is a command to just update
the Uuid as well.
Which we can see it over here.
There's a command C set Uid and we can provide the Uid into it.
So let's just run this command as well.
C set uid.
And we have to provide the Uid with without space.
So this is the actual Uid.
Right.
So let's just remove the space and let's just copy it and paste it over here and let's just hit enter.
So the Uuid is updated, as you can see.
Now let's just check out the Uuid one more time.
For its routing the correct Uid as well.
Right.
So this is how you create clone of any mifare classic card.
And then we can use this clone in place of actual card.
So these are few vulnerabilities in mifare classic card.
And and I already told you how to overcome these vulnerabilities.
You can change all the keys whenever you are updating or programming mifare classic cards.
You have to change the keys of all the sector trailers Key A and key B of all the sector trailers so
that your card is secure.